That's...Giorno's brooch?
C-could it be...alive?
I can't believe it!
It's forming a brand new hand!
Giorno's not going down
without a hell of a fight!
As long as I keep that
thing away from his hand,
Narancia and Mista might have a chance!
But how the hell do I do that?
What am I gonna do?!
God bless you.
And if you are the best man,
You can't break it and move on.
Woah, woah...
The miracles that make us.
To the world,
Don't care.
The peace of the door,
The body who will die.
The hope that we can live.
Hell no!
I must not utter a single sound.
And I can't move any
faster than the brooch,
or that thing will zero
in on me and attack.
I'm so sorry everyone
but I can't do anything
to help once it feeds
on the brooch it'll go
after me next now's my
chance to get out of
sight the closet I can
hide in there for now this
switch it must be the
chair's recline button of
course this will be my
ticket out of this nightmare
situation that beast
will catch sight of the
seat moving and shift
its focus to go after it
then i'll grab the brooch
and rush to the cockpit
what am i thinking i
can't do something like
that it's madness talk
about having a death
wish forget it i'll wait
this out in the closet
have i lost it it's like my
body just acted on its own
This isn't making sense.
I was determined to not press the
button, but then did it anyway.
Fine.
I'm gonna go for it.
It's now or never.
All right, Trish.
Take your time.
Move nice and slow, like a Tai Chi master.
Almost there.
Just two more meters.
Slow and deliberate.
Your life depends on it.
It's coming this way.
Shit, it already destroyed the seat!
Which means no more reclining it.
Don't panic.
Just make another seat recline.
What?
Why did it go after me and not the seat?
What's this liquid?
Did that fleshy horror react
to it dripping to the ground?
But why are my boots even
wet in the first place?
All I did was push the recline button.
So how the hell did they get drenched?
Damn it!
This is exactly why I didn't want
to go after that stupid ladybug!
I should have just stayed
out of this altogether!
Help me to drag me!
I'm going to die!
What my boot just fell
off my foot it's like
it slid around and passed through my leg I
don't understand any of
this what just happened
here's your opportunity procure
the brooch Quickly, Trish.
Who's there?
Who's speaking right now?
Someone who's always been here.
Since you were a little girl,
never once have I left your side.
Now, Trish, I'm asking you
to retrieve that brooch.
You've already made
the decision, you know.
Protecting Giorno's hand
started you down this road.
But your hesitation weakens you.
Act now.
What would you have me do?
Tell me, Trish. I...
I don't even know who you are.
That's quite simple.
I am your essence.
I am the force who repelled
that scum from your boot.
Your inner power given form.
Think of me as your unique ability. Huh?
Now, you've made your decision, so act.
You must protect Giorno's hand.
Get to it!
But Trish, by keeping it from harm, you
give Giorno and the others a chance at life.
And it gives you a chance, too.
What is happening?
Pick it up now! Hurry!
I'm about to die!
I don't know what to do or
how to protect this thing!
You do know what to do, Trish.
Our ability made the seat malleable.
What?
Malleable?
I know it's crazy, but I just
slipped right through the seat.
And I heard that
abomination in the process.
My powers ripped off a chunk of its body.
It can stop bullets,
catch up to a speeding plane,
and even annihilate objects moving
at high speeds without issue.
But when it hits a still object, it
breaks apart like hamburger meat.
Are you actually me?
I mean my essence.
And did I really just do all this?
My boot slipping off my foot.
That doesn't matter.
Not right now.
You've secured the brooch.
Your deep determination
overcame your cowardice.
You are growing much stronger, Trish.
Mentally and emotionally as well.
It's lovely to see.
Listen.
Your power is to transform any
matter into a malleable object.
The power to make things soft.
Yet even more durable than diamonds.
Here it comes!
You must remain completely still.
I finally get that we're the same entity.
But I've got to get out of sight!
Please, make the closet elastic! Hurry!
I'm begging you!
Stay away!
You're not getting in here! Get back!
Shit, it managed to sniff me out all
the way back here. I'm... I'm dead.
I know I'm supposed to
be a stand user now,
and I can use all of these
special powers or whatever.
But what good are they?
This thing's unstoppable!
Its users already dead!
For heaven's sakes!
Nothing can stop this murderous blob!
You see, this is why I
asked you to remain still.
Earlier, our primary
duty should be reaching!
But we went the other direction!
What are you talking about?
Journo's brooch is nothing but!
of Robbing Incubator at the moment.
I had to rescue it.
All this power does is soften stuff.
It's totally useless!
I can barely dodge these attacks!
Huh?
It went after the clock again?
What the?
The clock has been elasticized huh?
As long as your movements don't
exceed the speed of the second hand,
the clock should hold the
attention of the enemy,
giving you an opportunity to
escape and rush to the cockpit.
I told you to remain
still, but I misspoke.
I meant to move stealthily.
Slower than the second hand, at least.
In truth, you must move as
slowly as a glacier in winter.
All the while possessing
the power of an iron vice.
Time to pulverize this
rotten heap of meat.
I want to hear it scream.
Paris di merda.
Why don't you do us all
a favor and just die?
Make this easy on yourself We both
know you want to croak, so do it!
Die already!
It's breaking down into tiny pieces.
Is it evaporating?
After all that trouble,
this vile killer of a stand is now
just a pile of disintegrating flesh.
Um, what's your name?
I mean, do you have one?
If we're a team, what do I call you?
Call me Spicy Lady.
Huh.
Weird, but in a good way.
Thanks to your bravery, Mista and
Narancia won't die from their wounds now.
You know, Giorno Giovanna
sure is a special one.
Without a doubt, he's a giver of life.
But in addition, he is a catalyst.
Watching him has caused you to mature.
I'll make sure the engines
are working properly.
Luchirati, there's something
that you ought to know.
There's no need for us to worry.
Giorno's already begun his plan to...
Triss, whatever it is, it can wait!
Listen up.
Move slowly.
It's crucial that you
carefully inch toward me.
We're at 7,000 meters.
6,800.
6,600.
Damn it.
We're dropping like a sack of
rocks, but I don't know why.
As to why we're losing
altitude, I have the answer.
But even so, I'm at a complete
loss regarding what to do about it.
I hate to say it, but I'm stumped here.
What the heck are you
talking about, Bucurati?
What did I say about moving?
No.
Please, no.
Wait, what? There's no way.
How the hell did it even...
Giorno said the beast
latches onto moving objects.
Once they're captured, it devours them.
Right now, the plane's engines...
In a word, they've been... eaten!
Trish, keep looking forward.
You must remain calm.
Just keep moving toward me, nice and slow.
What's this?
What the hell is this monster?
It can't stop us from falling.
We're about to get up close
and personal with the ground.
Actually, we'd be lucky to hit the ground.
These engines are going to blow.
How did it survive?
It was torn to pieces and evaporated.
Shit, that's right.
The engine is located behind the closet.
Oh no.
A cell or two must have passed through
a crevice in the wall of the closet.
It must be having a field day
feeding on the power of the engine.
And now...
We're gonna have to crash land.
Aim for the Terranian Sea.
Prepare for a water landing.
It's our only hope.
An emergency landing.
Even if by some miracle we manage to land
on the water in one piece, then what?
It'll still try to hunt us down.
I can't find any weaknesses in this stand.
It's unstoppable.
Slow and steady, Trish.
Easy does it.
Move like a tiger closing in on its prey.
Calm and deliberate.
Don't run.
Doing so will just invite its attack.
What are you doing?
Weren't you listening?
It's gonna latch onto you!
Yeah, you're damn right it
will, but what does it matter?
The same thing will happen
even if I move like a slug.
So why not take the gamble?
Now get your ass back in
the cockpit, Butcherati!
You've completely lost your mind!
The door's not...
How the hell?
Miss Power. Don't tell me.
This girl is...
An emergency landing?
Sorry, but you've got the wrong idea.
If you want to live long enough to
see Sardinia with your own eyes,
we've no choice but to...
Bust this death trap!
Wannabe!
Spicy lady!
What in the world? These powers.
When did you get stand abilities?
The walls, the glass, everything
in here is elastic like rubber.
It's pretty obvious by now that this
meatloaf from Hell has a need for speed.
Well, the bastard's in luck.
A plane falling from the sky
moves faster than a parachute!
Eat it! Bitch meat!
That thing got us good,
but it's not all bad.
Now that our plane is nothing but smoldering
scrap metal at the bottom of the sea,
we should be safe.
This way,
the boss's henchmen
will never know whether
we survived or went down
in a blaze of glory.
It's genius, right?
We shook off the Family and
they never even saw it coming.
Which means we'll have
some time on our hands.
Time to hunt down the
bastard like a rabid dog
and show the world what
a coward he really is!
No, Abakio.
Much as I hate to say it,
we're not out of the woods.
That creature is still
hunting us this very moment.
But I'm gonna get rid of it for good.
My zipper will be more
than enough to end it.
How is it possible? We...
roasted it!
I'm at a loss.
This is unreal.
It has no weaknesses that I can see.
Our only chance is to follow Jono's
lead and use velocity to drive it out.
Wait, you don't mean what I think you do.
No, don't do it.
You're really gonna
let him feed on your...
Don't be a fool!
Do you want to be a hero so bad
you'll throw your life away?
Don't worry, Abakyo.
No one's throwing their
lives away anytime soon.
Jono's life-invigorating
essence is safe and sound.
And it's ready for action.
What?
When did you...
Arrivederci.
Notorious Chase.
It is known as the stand
that's impossible to kill,
but is tragically doomed to chase
the endless crash of the sea.
On the rare occasion a speeding
vessel moves faster than the waves,
it strikes out in a ravenous embrace.
The seas of its watery
purgatory would be known
to fishermen as the
bowels of the Tyrrhenian,
the waters where sailors go to die.
Now, let's pull our own disappearing
act and unmask this bastard boss.
Whatever he's hiding, we're gonna find it.
News agencies are reporting
that a private plane has crashed
into the Tyrrhenian Sea some 50
kilometers northeast of Sardinia?
shortly after taking off
from Marco Polo Airport.
At this time, the incident remains a mystery
all passengers remain unaccounted for.
I thought I might do away with the past,
Yet it still reveals
its rose-stained head.
Well, there goes my short-lived peace.
A mere interloper would
be an annoyance for sure.
But family...
Family makes this matter
so much more complicated.
But blood is simply blood.
Once I blot this aberration
out of existence,
I'll forever be the pinnacle
of success and status.
Several days after Pericolo
took responsibility for Trish,
those traitors scoured this apartment?
the one Trish and her
mother used to call home.
But none of them noticed.
Till recently, Trish greeted
the day from this very room.
And every day, she'd spend her
time poring over this photograph,
the one picture her mother loved
and cherished more than any other.
There's no confusing this date.
I'm certain of it.
It was 15 years ago.
Incredible that something like
this nearly slipped my notice.
Blast it!
Moronic, sentimental crash!
Their plane crashed and
burned, yet they live.
I feel it in my flesh.
My daughter's powers have awakened.
and her body practically radiates
life as she nears Sardinia.
If a Bacchios stand had any
involvement in flying that plane,
then there's no question that
bastard is also still alive.
Moody Jazz must never reach
the location in this picture.
It's repressed, but eventually
the memory will resurface.
I'm certain of that much.
She hasn't totally forgotten.
Once in Sardinia, the
memories will return.
She'll remember it was
here that it happened.
The man who took the photo of her
beautiful young mother 15 years ago was me.
That point in time must never be
subject to Moody Jazz's replay!
It's settled.
I have to go.
Alone.
This is the one task that
I can only entrust myself.
Oh my i i'm terribly sorry i knocked
but um i'm here to clean your room.
Please you must forgive me
i'll return a bit later.
Huh.
Dear me now just what was
i doing in here again?
Oh yes how could i forget i have to
clean the room time waits for no one.
They're accusing!
Not always we are knowing.
What is just fiction?
Or what is the truth?
They have a mission.
They are the passion.
But they dare to tell us
What's bad and what's good.
Stand up!
Join us!
Come on!
To save us a lie.
We are the power!
Cause they're the future!
Cause we are fighters!
Just fighting for a ride.
Thank you.